

MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

Details

+491637979815

ulgacemre@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

Python

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

Pandas

Tensorflow

OpenCV

Flask

Streamlit

Laravel

Git

Google Cloud

AWS

Ability to Work in a Team

Communication Skills

Critical thinking and problem solving

Languages

English

German

Turkish

Profile

Passionate Machine Learning Engineer with 4 years of experience with various machine learning projects including Computer Vision and Data Science. Highly accurate and experienced Data Scientist adept at collecting, analyzing, and interpreting large datasets, developing new forecasting models, and performing data management tasks.

Employment History

Al Instructor, Kodluyoruz, Istanbul

MARCH 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence
- Basic Python
- Introduction to Machine Learning

Computer Vision Engineer, GreenBrainAI, Istanbul

JANUARY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

- Collected, studied, and interpreted large datasets
- · Recycle using image processing
- Tensorflow object detection api
- Embedded system Jetson Nano

Machine Learning Engineer, Globalaihub, Switzerland

APRIL 2020 - PRESENT

- Designed, implemented and evaluated new models
- Machine learning at Google cloud
- Deployment of models with Flask Api
- Web development

Data Scientist, Clarusway LLC, United States

JUNE 2020 - PRESENT

- Developed and implemented new forecasting models which increased company productivity and efficiency.
- Developing projects based on e-commerce: Customer Segmantation and Rfm analysis, Fraud detection, Churn prediction
- Pipelining in Google cloud environment
- Deployment with Streamlit

Upwork Freelancer, Upwork

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

- Computer Vision
- Training and testing machine learning models
- Deep learning
- Development of REST services
- · Integrating machine learning algorithms

Education

Bachelor, Marmara University, Istanbul

JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2019

I developed style transfer android application with computer vision technique that allows us to recompose the content of an image in the style of another. If you've ever imagined what a photo might look like if it were painted by a famous artist, then style transfer is the computer vision technique that turns this into a reality.